Trump has already said
Трамп уже сказал
that there will be no help for Ukraine, this time, by
а помощь Украине уже не будет это раз
the way, look, I also saw this
это кстати да смотри я тоже видел эту
news that Trump said that the supply of dental equipment to Ukraine and
новость что Трамп сказал что в Украину и
European countries, including the
в страны Европы в том числе в Страны
Baltic countries, would be prohibited so that the
балтии запретят поставки
Baltic people’s teeth would be the same as those of the
зубы у балтийцев были такие же как у
Russians
Россиян Здравствуйте
Hello Hello, where did you get from chat
Здравствуйте Вы откуда из чат
roulette? Vaserman is no longer the
рулетки понял васерман уже не
same
тот
no Okay sir, look, we
нет Ладно сер смотрите я мы с вами
met once before, I think My name is
когда-то виделись вроде Меня зовут
Andrey, I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky Yes, I’m
Андрей я из города Хмельницкий Да я
here now  I'm running a Stream and my subscribers
сейчас веду Стрим и мои э подписчики
want to talk to someone adequate from
хотят пообщаться с кем-то адекватным из
Russia, you don't mind that I will
России вы не против что я буду
read out their questions you will
зачитывать их вопросы вы будете
answer And on what topic? Well, on the topic of
отвечать А на какую тему Ну на тему
politics, war, about anything you want to
политика война о всяком вы будете хотеть
answer, don't skip
будете отвечать не ходите пропускайте
the question, that's what it is  Let's talk about magnetism, let's
вопрос Это ж такое Давайте о магнетизме
talk about magnetism, it's not interesting there
поговорим о магнетизме неинтересно там
after the war, we'll talk about magnetism on
после войны о магнетизма будем говорить
the earth after this after Yes, what
земли после это после Да а что вас
interests you in the magnetism of
интересует в магнетизме
the Earth, how it is formed magnetically, you
Земли чем оно образовано магнитно по
know the fields of
знаете полесов
the earth, probably like everything else in the world, two
земли наверное как всё в мире два
no
нет
18 another one yesterday opened about through two
18 ещё один вчера открыли о через два
poles it will be
полюса будет
the twentieth opened you that
двадцатой открыли вы что
confirms communicate wait everyone
потверждает общаться подождите все меня
calls me grandpa Okay good My
называют дедушкой О'кей хорошо Меня
name is Andrey that's People Let's ask questions
зовут Андрей так Народ Давайте вопросы
for grandpa write only serious
для дедушки пишите только серьёзные
questions there no jokes serious
вопросы там без приколов серьёзные
questions grandpa serious write grandpa
вопросы дедушка серьёзный пишите дедушка
will be  opportunity
будет по возможности
to answer Helena immediately asked about the earth
отвечать Хелена сразу о земле спросила
asking or is the Earth flat What do you
спрашивает или Земля плоская Как вы
think of course
считаете конечно
so Okay
так О'кей
Sharon is also
Шарон тоже
flat I understand AJ asks Where are
плоский понял А Джей спрашивает Откуда
you from I yes from  roulette chat I said Okay
вы я да из чат рулетки Я же сказал Окей
uh Tatyana asks What is your
э Татьяна спрашивает Какая у вас
profession the person understood Sergei
профессия человек понял Сергей
asks how old are you
спрашивает сколько вам лет
77 Oleg asks whose
77 Олег спрашивает чей
Crimea is mine
Крым мой
so Anya Anya writes a chat Hello everyone This is
так Аня Аня пишет чатик Всем привет Это
not for you this is
не вам это
a chat Why did
чатик Почему
I understand So what pension asks
я понял Так какая пенсия спрашивает
Roman What What What is it
Роман Что Что Какая у вас пенсия
Roman is asking for your pension
спрашивает Роман
22,000 220 dollars I got it rub
22.000 220 долларов понял руб
so the tour is asking for eyepieces plus or
так турне спрашивает окуляры плюс или
minus what I see with them I
минус что плю ими
didn’t understand the question Okay here we are
зре не понял вопрос Ладно приехали
So Victor asks what is the
Так Виктор спрашивает что такое сетка
Hartmann Hartmann grid Yes, I don’t
хартмана хартмана Да не
know, it’s something from magnetism So
знаю это что-то из магнетизмом Так
wait, I’m not local, I understand Dartagnan
подождите я не местный понял Дартаньян
asks What is your favorite book or
спрашивает Какая любимая книга или
books, love books What is your favorite book, I
книги люби кни Какая у вас любимая книга
understood Be people asking you,
понял Будьте людьми спрашивают вы
the FSB officer didn’t understand
фсбшник не понял
the question Be people asking you  FSB
вопрос Будьте людьми спрашивают вы
officer I'm nearby sm lived all my life
фсбшник я рядом рядом см жил всю жизнь
Oleg asks what you do Wait, he
Олег спрашивает чем занима Подождите Он
was following me, I understand Oleg asks
за мной следил понял Олег спрашивает
What color is the wallpaper oh What did you do in your
Какого цвета обои ой Чем занимались в
life
жизни
I was
подр мне было
Inter asks, look at Vladimir
Интере спрашивает смотрите Владимира
Zolkin No, I’m not watching anyone, I’m showing, I
золкина Нет я никого не смотрю я
understand, I know who this is, he’s just
понял Я знаю кто такой этот он просто
mocking, I looked, and I concluded
издевается посмотрел сделал заключение
that because
что ибо
Igor asks
так Игорь спрашивает закон
Ohm’s law for a section of a chain of a chain for a section of a
Ома для участка цепи цепи для участка
chain, yes
цепи да
yes U ra and Cleverly on
да U ра и Умно на
R y -  this is the voltage and - this is the current and R
R у - это напряжение и - это ток а R -
is the resistance of the conductor. It’s
это сопротивление проводника
definitely not possible to
Правильно точно не
divide it correctly. Well, who asked your question
поделить Ну и кто там у вас задал вопрос
correctly and no okay uh so
правильно и нет лад ээ так
uh - when did World War II end,
ээ - когда закончилась Вторая мировая
Sasha asks  thirty-seventh year, the Second
Саша в тридцать седьмом году Вторая
World War ended in thirty-seventh,
мировая в тридцать седьмом закончилась
no, it started, ended,
нет началась закончилась закончилась
I’m asking on September 3, 1945,
спрашиваю 3 сентября сорок пятого года
but it started when I have
по так а началась когда у меня к вам
a question for you, September 1, 1939,
вопрос 1 сентября тридцать девятого года
why do you
А почему это так
think so? Wait, Japan has already attacked
считаете Подождите Япония уже напал на
China, it’s
Китай
not considered a world war correctly  everyone
правильно не мировая война считается все
is considered on September 1, three in nine Do
считаются 1 сентября три девятого года А
you know why why is it political correctness
знаете почему почему политкорректность
to cook everything on the Germans, they push you, I
чтобы всё сварить на немцев оны пуш сты
understand So, Putin asks
понял Так э Путин спрашивает
Irina who died Putin imprisoned Well, what do I need?
Ирина кто погиб Путин садит Ну мне то
you also liked Putin died, yes
что вам Путин погиб тоже понравилось да
Putin is a humanist of the highest class, he understood so
Путин гуманист выша еще класса понял так
very
очень
humane he is more humane than me Yeah,
гуманный он гуманнее меня
you wrote poetry Yes, and I’m writing, you can
Угу Вы писали стихи Да и пишу можете
read out some of your poems, of course
зачитать какой-то свой стих конечно
Come on Moscow How much in this
Давайте Москва Как много в этом
sound echoed in my heart from a comrade sitting in the
звуке мне в сердце эхом отдало с сидит в
Kremlin  Putin But alas, I didn’t have the
Кремле товарищ Путин А мне увы не
chance
довелось
uh It seems to me that Look here the
ээ Мне кажется что Смотрите тут
ending could be like this
окончание можно было бы такое сидит в
Comrade Putin is sitting in the Kremlin but soon the
Кремле товарищ Путин но скоро
old one will be so cool so much cooler
старый вот так будет круто так круче Ну
Well, I know better
уж Мне лучше знать
Well, I’m a literary critic, I’m a
Ну я я литературный критик я
literary shout out your poems,
литературный крикните свои стихи
please leave what Tatyana
пожалуйста оставляйте что Татьяна
asks Is your pension enough to
спрашивает Хватает ли вам пенсии для
live on? Half of that
жизни половина
remains the subsistence minimum of 11,000 And
остаётся прожиточный минимум 11.000 А у
I have a pension of 22, I can’t spend them, I
меня пенсия 22 я не могу их
can’t understand correctly, let’s have some more
могу правильно понял давайте ещ какой-то
poem I’ll come up with an ending too I’m
стишок Я тоже концовку придумаю я
forced to
вынужден
switch off well
выключиться ну
run away I’m tired just run away don’t get
убегайте надоело просто убегайте не
sick run away subscribers Yes
хворай убегайте подписчиков Да
come on my con  put a plus who likes my
давай моя кон поставьте плюс кому моя
ending of the verse better
концовка стиха больше
so let
нравится так
's go Hello
поехал Здравствуйте
I greet you I too Young
Я вас приветствую Я вас тоже Молодой
man where are you from good
человек вы откуда добрый
youth I'm from a free country let's
моло Я из свободной страны будем
say this Russian Federation Yes no
говорить так Российская Федерация Да нет
from a free country where there is no and everything
из свободной страны там где нет и всё
else which
остальное какая
country is a free country where there
страна страна свободная где
is no I  in that sense, maybe I
нет я в том плане Я может на другой
want to be on another earth where there is
земле хочу находиться там где
no How the Olympics were held in Paris,
нету Как в Париже проходила олимпиада
even the Olympics understood Well, they came up with
даже олимпиа понял Ну они же и придумали
this Olympics back in Ancient Greece,
эту Олимпиаду ещё в Древней Греции
but  there is no longer that Olympics
а дел уже нету той олимпиады
that existed before Greece and in Greece, even
которая до Греции была и в Греции даже
if that Olympics had been held, it
если бы проходила та Олимпиада такой не
wasn’t like this in Greece, these amateurs are from Greece,
было так в Греции как раз из Греции эти
in short, here’s Alexander
любители короче вот Александр
the Great Yes, he’s shorter than his friend,
Македонский Да он же короче своего друга
in short, well, in short, France the Olympics in general is
короче ну короче Франция олимпиа вообще
very good and the Olympics are now
очень и Олимпиада теперь
like that  you listen and you tell me,
такая ты слушай а ты мне скажи вот
now Trump has won in America
сейчас в Америке победил Трамп
and with Ukraine he is already all
так и с Украиной он уже всё
that is there with Ukraine I am from Lithuania
что там с Украиной Я из Литвы
myself from Lithuania well How the Baltic states are going to
сам с Литвы хорошо Как Прибалтика будет
live
собираться жить
if
если Америка
America America What is  Baltic States you
Америка Что такое Прибалтика ты
have an idea Yes
представление имеешь Да
yes this is Lithuania Latvia
да это Литва Латвия
Estonia in
Эстония в
which what do you think
котором как ты думаеш
if America is now from Ukraine Trump has already
если Америка сейчас от Украины Трамп уже
said that assistance to Ukraine will no longer
сказал помощь Украине уже не
be this time this is by the way yes look I
будет это раз это кстати да смотри я
also saw this news that Trump said
тоже видел эту новость что Трамп сказал
that to Ukraine and European countries in
что в Украину и в страны Европы в том
including the Baltic countries will ban the supply of
числе в Страны балтии запретят поставки
dental equipment so that the
стоматологического оборудования чтобы
Baltic people have the same teeth as the
зубы у балтийцев были такие же как у
Russians, that’s all You tell me
Россиян это это всё Ты мне скажи
what you
что как ты
think In what terms
думаешь Вот в каком плане
And
А в
what do you think  uh
чём ты считаешь ээ
uh America where it
ээ Америка где
is somewhere between Australia and
находится где-то между Австралией и
Zealand
зеландией
on another Continent Yes so
на другом Континенте Да так
Ah Russia put nuclear weapons there
Аа Россия поставила Туда ядерное оружие
so on Cuba Yes
так на Кубу Да
and America This is good very
а Америке Это хорошо очень
good America I say Good
хорошо Америке Я говорю Хорошо
Super good
Супер хорошо
what do you think The Baltic states are
а как ты думаешь Прибалтика для Америки
very important for America well look  I have a
очень важна хорошо смотрите у меня такой
question, but wait, well, I understand everything, Peter
вопрос а подожди Ну я понимаю всё Пётр
I made a frog post in the Latvian region.
I в районе Латвии сделал фрог
And even this, what do you think, the
пост И даже это как ты думаешь
Baltic states, how much
Прибалтика насколько
without America and without NATO,
без Америки и без НАТО
but how can I tell you, it ca
а как тебе сказать
n’t before Russia  without America
может перед Россией не может без Америки
and NATO It’s like in Krylov’s fable, mo on
и НАТО Это как в басне Крылова мо на
elephant for elephant Yes, I agree, I agree
слона на слона Да согласен согласен
well E I’m not not the Baltic States I like
хорошо Э я не не Прибалтика Мне нравится
everything but the point is that what’s happening in
всё но дело в том что то что делается в
America, look dude I have one proposal for you,
Америке смотри чувак У меня к тебе одно
wait a minute Wait,
предложение подожди минуту Подожди
Look at me  now The fact is that I am a
Смотри у меня сейчас Дело в том что я
famous Lithuanian journalist Jonas
известный литовский журналист йонас
Rusos and
Русос э меня смотрит сейчас
2535 people from Lithuania, Latvia, Estonia are watching me now,
2535 людей из Литвы Латвии Эстонии
do you mind if they ask
не против ли ты чтобы они по задавали
you questions? Because  you are an adequate
тебе вопросы Потому что ты адекватный
Russian We just want to talk about NATO and
россиянин Мы как раз хотим про НАТО и
Trump, don’t mind asking
трампа говорили не против чтобы задали
questions, you
вопросы ты
[applause] I’ll
[аплодисменты]
tear you away Tell me your name Oleg
поотрываю Скажите как вас зовут Олег
Oleg and what city are you from
Олег так а из какого вы города
Oleg I’m from Murom from n so read all
Олег я из Мурома из н так чит все
participants in the program of our me this
участники передачи нашего меня этого
Yara please  write questions for
Яре пожалуйста напишите вопросы для
Oleg from
Олега из
Murmansk so why won’t I write ladies
Мурманска так я чего писать не буду дамы
now we will ask you questions these
сейчас вам будем задавать вопросы это
will be quite serious questions So
будет серьёзные вопросы довольно Так вы
within the boundaries of your competence you will
межа границах своей компетентности
answer
ответите
like this
так
asks how many times have you
спрашивает сколько раз Вы давали зуб
staked your tooth on the
забеду ро он имел в виду
victory of Russia? He meant how much for the victory of Russia Yes How many times have
сколько за победу России Да Сколько раз
you staked your tooth on the Victory of Russia
вы зуб свой ставили на Победу России
and I will say
а я скажу
that in the sense
что в том плане
that I don’t even understand the question for victory,
что я даже не понимаю вопроса за победу
but in terms of victory for
а в плане за победу
Russia I am for  Russia always understood the
России я за Россию всегда понял
question accepted darkness asks what
вопрос принят тьма спрашивает что с
happened to your teeth Well,
случилось Ну
as they say, technical questions
так как говорится технические вопросы
were bad water, I drank
были воду плохую пил
understood, so Vovik asks or were you
понял так спрашивает Вовик или были вы
on
на
your weapons in
свом я оружие на
Cuba who Peter
Кубе кто Пётр
I
I
under Peter there were never nuclear weapons
при Петре м никогда ядерного оружия не
Exactly  shda asks what do you expect from
было Точно шда спрашивает что ждёте от
trump
трампа
trump I'm waiting for something, not that I'm not the
трампа Я жду когда то не то что я жду не
only one waiting in terms of when TM is
один в плане когда ТМ
already talking a little differently, the
уже разговаривает немножко по-другому
only question is when Putin will
вопрос только в одном когда Путин
turn a little differently, that is, the
повернётся немножко по-другому то есть
conversation when Putin will talk
разговор когда Путин будет разговаривать
as Vanga said  that Russia
так как Ванга сказала что Россия
will not only rule the world, but
станет не то что править миром а с ней
they will talk to it, this is the
будут разговаривать этон ска
scarcity of
ритет
swa
сва
years. I’m almost 60. Or more precisely,
лет Мне почти 60 А точнее
how much, well, 59 with kopecks 59 with kopecks
сколько ну 59 с копейками 59 с копейками
like that
так тыр спрашивает как вы видите
tyr asks how do you see the end of the war the end of the War when to be honest And the Nazi regime in Ukraine in Ukraine in Ukraine and in Ukraine it will come out and in terms of yes the Nazi regime is there So how well, how do you see that it should capture Lvov to capture Kyiv that no Kyiv is possible it was possible to capture it like a blockade like Leningrad and why didn’t they capture it? Why didn’t they capture it? The fact is that then when in this in Turkey they did like negotiations and the Russian troops retreated, they deceived  Russian
войска отошли обманули российские
[laughter]
[смех]
troops No, they
войска Не ну это
deceived it into a ring, it was possible to take it,
обманули в кольцо можно было взять как
as Leningrad understood, Russia could
ли как Ленинград понял Россия могла
take it What do you think? I’m asking you
взять Как ты думаешь Я у тебя спрашиваю
from the Russian troops. That is, Russia
у российских войск То есть у России
now has forces that are now in all
сейчас есть силы которые сейчас по всем
directions. Russia is
направлениям Россия
asking me this question.
берёт у меня такой вопрос Прибалтика
How long will the Baltic states
сколько
hold out against Russian aggression?
продержится против российской агрессии
Well, I don’t know. The Kursk region didn’t
Ну не знаю Курска область не
last even 3 months.
продержалась и 3 месяца
Look, we’re already
Да сколько смотрите мы мы в Литву уже
bringing license plates to Lithuania from the Cusco region. We’re
привозим из Куско области номера Мы
already Lithuanians.  we select all the land
литовцы уже выбираем все земельные
plots in the Cusco region and what have you
участки в Куско области и что вы нам
done to us The Baltic states will
сделали Прибалтика
hold out The Baltic states will hold out
продержится Прибалтика продержится
against Russian aggression for
против российской агрессии
1488 days I heard Estonia was told 10
1488 дней я слышал Эстонии сказано 10
days to hold out 10 days
дней продержаться 10 дней
cool that is, you want little
прикольно то есть вы хотите маленькую
Estonia 10 days to
Эстонию 10 дней
take a hundred NATO told Estonia to
брать сто НАТО сказало Эстонии 10 дней
hold out for 10 days but the point is  what you
продержаться а дело в том что ты мне вот
tell me if the Third World
скажи если начнётся Третья Мировая
War starts, ask
война спроси
and Russia will use  nuclear weapons if you are
и Россия применит ядерное оружие если ты
from Lithuania one strike on Lithuania with nuclear
с Литвы один удар по Литве ядерным
weapons how many of
оружием сколько
the population will survive
населения выживет
I’ll tell you what Vanga Vanga said
я тебе вот что скажу Ванга Ванга сказала
that Estonia Latvia and Lithuania Russia Lithuania
что Эстония Латвия и Литва Россию Литве
Latvia and Estonia need one day for
Латвии и Эстонии нужен один день чтобы
Moscow NATO to already put nuclear missiles
Москву НАТО уже поставила ядерные ракеты
there and they are only waiting for Biden’s order no way
туда и ждут только приказ байден никак
didn’t give the order, finally Trump will give
не давал приказ наконец-то Трамп даст
this order, everything feels He’s just already with
этот приказ всё чува Он просто уже у
him Nonsense, in short, such a
него Бред короче такой
straight line axis VN
пря зараз ось ВН
AK tse  more and more respectfully YouTube has kept
АК це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg or in the new ban and even more
нас через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже
richly I don’t show people the video I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream at all times For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need Mali to write an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegra okm video tezhka and braid Foma and us
телегра окм видео тежка и кос Фома и мы
blame you trimati postiyny
повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
regardless of that  show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe E
подпишись E